[
	{
		"title": "Experiments!",
		"modules": [
			{
				"title": "Parse trees",
				"slides": []
			}
		]
	},        
	{
		"title": "Alphabet",
		"modules": [
			{
				"title": "Alphabet",
				"slides": [
					{	
						"type": "slide_info",
						"includeHTML": "/static/content/en/slides/1.alphabet/intro.html"
					},
					{
						"type": "slide_info",
						"includeHTML": "/static/content/en/slides/1.alphabet/alpha.html"
					},
					{
						"type": "slide_info",
						"includeHTML": "/static/content/en/slides/1.alphabet/beta.html"
					},
					{
						"type": "slide_info",
						"includeHTML": "/static/content/en/slides/1.alphabet/gamma.html"
					},
					{
						"type": "slide_direct_select",
						"settings": { "orientation": "vertical" },
						"title": "Identify the letter!",
						"question": "How does <strong lang=\"grc\">β</strong> sound and what is it called?",
						"options": [ [
							{ "value": "gamma - gigantic", "display": "Gamma - like <u>g</u>iant" },
							{ "value": "gamma - good", "display": "Gamma - like <u>g</u>ood" },
							{ "value": "sigma - signal", "display": "Sigma - like <u>s</u>ignal" },
							{ "value": "beta - book", "display": "Beta - like <u>b</u>ook" }
						]],
						"answers": ["beta - book"],
						"successMsg": "<strong>Right Answer!</strong> Remember that Beta sounds like the \"b\" in book.",
						"hintMsg": "<strong>Not Quite.</strong> The correct answer was <strong>beta like book.</strong>",
						"failureMsg": "<strong>The correct answer was beta like book</strong>",
						"require_order": "false",
						"require_all": "true"
					},
					{
						"type": "slide_direct_select",
						"settings": { "orientation": "horizontal" },
						"title": "Identify the letter!",
						"question": "Which of these are <strong>gammas</strong>?",
						"options": [ [
							{ "value": "Α", "display": "<span lang=\"grc\">Α</span>" },
							{ "value": "α", "display": "<span lang=\"grc\">α</span>" },
							{ "value": "Β", "display": "<span lang=\"grc\">Β</span>" },
							{ "value": "β", "display": "<span lang=\"grc\">β</span>" },
							{ "value": "Γ", "display": "<span lang=\"grc\">Γ</span>" },
							{ "value": "γ", "display": "<span lang=\"grc\">γ</span>" }
						]],
						"answers": ["γ", "Γ"],
						"successMsg": "<strong>Right Answer!</strong> You've identified gamma, <span class=\"grc\">Γ γ</span>, pronounced like the \"g\" in <u>g</u>rammar.",
						"hintMsg": "<strong>Not Quite.</strong>The correct answer was <strong><span class=\"grc\">Γ γ</span>.</strong>",
						"failureMsg": "<strong>The correct answer <span class=\"grc\">Γ γ</span>.</strong>",
						"require_order": "false",
						"require_all": "true"
					},
					{
						"type": "slide_direct_select",
						"settings": { "orientation": "vertical" },
						"title": "Identify the letter!",
						"question": "How does <strong lang=\"grc\">γ</strong> sound and what is it called?",
						"options": [ [
							{ "value": "gamma - gigantic", "display": "Gamma - like <u>g</u>iant" },
							{ "value": "gamma - grammar", "display": "Gamma - like <u>g</u>rammar" },
							{ "value": "sigma - signal", "display": "Sigma - like <u>s</u>ignal" },
							{ "value": "beta - book", "display": "Beta - like <u>b</u>ook" }
						]],
						"answers": ["gamma - grammar"],
						"successMsg": "<strong>Right Answer!</strong> ",
						"hintMsg": "<strong>Not Quite.</strong> Remember that gamma sounds like the <strong>\"g\" in grammar.</strong>",
						"failureMsg": "<strong>The correct answer was \"g\" like grammar.</strong>",
						"require_order": "false",
						"require_all": "true"
					},
					{
						"type": "slide_direct_select",
						"settings": { "orientation": "vertical" },
						"title": "Identify the letter!",
						"question": "Which of these is an <strong>alpha</strong>?",
						"options": [ [
							{ "value": "α", "display": "<span lang=\"grc\">α</span>" },
							{ "value": "β", "display": "<span lang=\"grc\">β</span>" },
							{ "value": "γ", "display": "<span lang=\"grc\">γ</span>" }
						]],
						"answers": ["α"],
						"successMsg": "<strong>Right Answer!</strong> You've identified alpha, <span class=\"grc\">α</span>, pronounced like the \"a\" in <u>a</u>rachnid.",
						"hintMsg": "<strong>Not Quite.</strong> The correct answer was <strong><span class=\"grc\">α</span>.</strong>",
						"failureMsg": "<strong>The correct answer was <span class=\"grc\">α</span>.</strong>",
						"require_order": "false",
						"require_all": "true"
					},
					{
						"type": "slide_multi_comp",
						"title": "Identify the letter!",
						"question": "What is the order of these letters in the alphabet?",
						"options": [ [
							{ "value": "β", "display": "<span lang=\"grc\">β</span>" },
							{ "value": "α", "display": "<span lang=\"grc\">α</span>" },
							{ "value": "γ", "display": "<span lang=\"grc\">γ</span>" }
						]],
						"answers": ["α", "β", "γ"],
						"successMsg": "Correctomundo!",
						"hintMsg": "<strong>Not Quite.</strong>The correct answer was <strong><span lang=\"grc\">α</span>, <span lang=\"grc\">β</span>, <span lang=\"grc\">γ</span>.</strong></strong>",
						"failureMsg": "<strong>The correct answer was <span lang=\"grc\">α</span>, <span lang=\"grc\">β</span>, <span lang=\"grc\">γ</span>.</strong>",
						"require_order": "true",
						"require_all": "true"
					},
					{
						"type": "slide_info",
						"includeHTML": "/static/content/en/slides/1.alphabet/delta.html"
					},
					{
						"type": "slide_info",
						"includeHTML": "/static/content/en/slides/1.alphabet/epsilon.html"
					},
					{
						"type": "slide_info",
						"includeHTML": "/static/content/en/slides/1.alphabet/zeta.html"
					},
					{
						"type": "slide_info",
						"includeHTML": "/static/content/en/slides/1.alphabet/eta.html"
					},
					{
						"type": "slide_info",
						"includeHTML": "/static/content/en/slides/1.alphabet/theta.html"
					},
					{
						"type": "slide_info",
						"includeHTML": "/static/content/en/slides/1.alphabet/iota.html"
					},
					{
						"type": "slide_info",
						"includeHTML": "/static/content/en/slides/1.alphabet/kappa.html"
					},
					{
						"type": "slide_info",
						"includeHTML": "/static/content/en/slides/1.alphabet/lambda.html"
					},
					{
						"type": "slide_direct_select",
						"settings": { "orientation": "vertical" },
						"title": "Identify the letter!",
						"question": "How does <strong lang=\"grc\">η</strong> sound and what is it called?",
						"options": [ [
							{ "value": "epsilon - get", "display": "Epsilon - like g<u>e</u>t" },
							{ "value": "mu - mouse", "display": "Mu - like <u>m</u>ouse" },
							{ "value": "eta - hair", "display": "Eta - like h<u>ai</u>r" },
							{ "value": "eta - eat", "display": "Eta - like <u>ea</u>t" }
						]],
						"answers": ["eta - hair"],
						"successMsg": "<strong>Right Answer!</strong> Remember that Eta sounds like the \"η\" in hair.",
						"hintMsg": "<strong>Not Quite.</strong> The correct answer was <strong>eta like hair.</strong>",
						"failureMsg": "<strong>The correct answer was eta like hair.</strong>",
						"require_order": "false",
						"require_all": "true"
					},
					{
						"type": "slide_direct_select",
						"settings": { "orientation": "horizontal" },
						"title": "Identify the letter!",
						"question": "Which of these are <strong>zdeta</strong>?",
						"options": [ [
							{ "value": "ζ", "display": "<span lang=\"grc\">ζ</span>" },
							{ "value": "Ζ", "display": "<span lang=\"grc\">Ζ</span>" },
							{ "value": "Η", "display": "<span lang=\"grc\">Η</span>" },
							{ "value": "η", "display": "<span lang=\"grc\">η</span>" },
							{ "value": "θ", "display": "<span lang=\"grc\">θ</span>" },
							{ "value": "Θ", "display": "<span lang=\"grc\">Θ</span>" }	
						]],
						"answers": ["ζ", "Ζ"],
						"successMsg": "<strong>Right Answer!</strong> You've identified zdeta, <span class=\"grc\">Ζ ζ</span>, pronounced like the \"zd\" in wi<u>sd</u>om.",
						"hintMsg": "<strong>Not Quite.</strong> The correct answer was <strong><span class=\"grc\">Ζ ζ</span></strong>",
						"failureMsg": "<strong>The correct answer was <span class=\"grc\">Ζ ζ</span>.</strong>",
						"require_order": "false",
						"require_all": "true"
					},
					{
						"type": "slide_direct_select",
						"settings": { "orientation": "vertical" },
						"title": "Identify the letter!",
						"question": "How does <strong lang=\"grc\">δ</strong> sound and what is it called?",
						"options": [ [
							{ "value": "gamma - gigantic", "display": "Gamma - like <u>g</u>iant" },
							{ "value": "delta - door", "display": "Delta - like <u>d</u>oor" },
							{ "value": "eta - hair", "display": "Eta - like h<u>ai</u>r" },
							{ "value": "sigma - signal", "display": "Sigma - like <u>s</u>ignal" }
						]],
						"answers": ["delta - door"],
						"successMsg": "<strong>Right Answer!</strong> Remember that delta sounds like the \"δ\" in door.",
						"hintMsg": "<strong>Not Quite.</strong> The correct answer was <strong>delta like door.</strong>",
						"failureMsg": "<strong>The correct answer was delta like door.</strong>",
						"require_order": "false",
						"require_all": "true"
					},
					{
						"type": "slide_direct_select",
						"settings": { "orientation": "vertical" },
						"title": "Identify the letter!",
						"question": "How does <strong lang=\"grc\">λ</strong> sound and what is it called?",
						"options": [ [
							{ "value": "gamma - gigantic", "display": "Gamma - like <u>g</u>iant" },
							{ "value": "lambda - long", "display": "Lambda - like <u>l</u>ong" },
							{ "value": "zdeta - wisdom", "display": "Zdeta - like wi<u>sd</u>om" },
							{ "value": "gamma - grammar", "display": "Gamma - like <u>g</u>rammar" }
						]],
						"answers": ["lambda - long"],
						"successMsg": "<strong>Right Answer!</strong>",
						"hintMsg": "<strong>Not Quite.</strong> Remember that lambda sounds like the <strong>\"λ\" in long.</strong>",
						"failureMsg": "<strong>The correct answer was \"λ\" in long.</strong>",
						"require_order": "false",
						"require_all": "true"
					},
					{
						"type": "slide_direct_select",
						"settings": { "orientation": "vertical" },
						"title": "Identify the letter!",
						"question": "Which of these is a <strong>theta</strong>?",
						"options": [ [
							{ "value": "ζ", "display": "<span lang=\"grc\">ζ</span>" },
							{ "value": "θ", "display": "<span lang=\"grc\">θ</span>" },
							{ "value": "γ", "display": "<span lang=\"grc\">γ</span>" }
						]],
						"answers": ["θ"],
						"successMsg": "<strong>Right Answer!</strong> You've identified theta, <span class=\"grc\">θ</span>, pronounced like the \"th\" in <u>th</u>under.",
						"hintMsg": "<strong>Not Quite.</strong> The correct answer was <strong>\"th\" like <u>th</u>under</strong>",
						"failureMsg": "<strong>The correct answer was \"th\" like <u>th</u>under.</strong>",
						"require_order": "false",
						"require_all": "true"
					},
					{
						"type": "slide_multi_comp",
						"title": "Identify the letter!",
						"question": "What is the order of these letters in the alphabet?",
						"options": [ [
							{ "value": "ζ", "display": "<span lang=\"grc\">ζ</span>" },
							{ "value": "δ", "display": "<span lang=\"grc\">δ</span>" },
							{ "value": "ε", "display": "<span lang=\"grc\">ε</span>" },
							{ "value": "η", "display": "<span lang=\"grc\">η</span>" }
						]],
						"answers": ["δ", "ε", "ζ", "η"],
						"successMsg": "You're right!",
						"hintMsg": "<strong>Not Quite.</strong> The correct answer was <span lang=\"grc\">δ</span>, <span lang=\"grc\">ε</span>, <span lang=\"grc\">ζ</span>, <span lang=\"grc\">η</span></strong>",
						"failureMsg": "<strong>The correct answer was <span lang=\"grc\">δ</span>, <span lang=\"grc\">ε</span>, <span lang=\"grc\">ζ</span>, <span lang=\"grc\">η</span></strong>",
						"require_order": "true",
						"require_all": "true"
					},
					{
						"type": "slide_direct_select",
						"settings": { "orientation": "vertical" },
						"title": "Identify the letter!",
						"question": "How does <strong lang=\"grc\">κ</strong> sound and what is it called?",
						"options": [ [
							{ "value": "gamma - gigantic", "display": "Gamma - like <u>g</u>iant" },
							{ "value": "kappa - coat", "display": "Kappa - like <u>c</u>oat" },
							{ "value": "zdeta - wisdom", "display": "Zdeta - like wi<u>sd</u>om" },
							{ "value": "kappa - cherry", "display": "Kappa - like <u>ch</u>erry" }
						]],
						"answers": ["kappa - coat"],
						"successMsg": "<strong>Right Answer!</strong>",
						"hintMsg": "<strong>Not Quite.</strong> Remember that gamma sounds like the <strong>\"κ\" in coat.",
						"failureMsg": "<strong>The correct answer was kappa like coat.</strong>",
						"require_order": "false",
						"require_all": "true"
					},
					{
						"type": "slide_direct_select",
						"settings": { "orientation": "vertical" },
						"title": "Identify the letter!",
						"question": "Which of these is a <strong>iota</strong>?",
						"options": [ [
							{ "value": "λ", "display": "<span lang=\"grc\">λ</span>" },
							{ "value": "ι", "display": "<span lang=\"grc\">ι</span>" },
							{ "value": "η", "display": "<span lang=\"grc\">η</span>" }
						]],
						"answers": ["ι"],
						"successMsg": "<strong>Right Answer!</strong> You've identified theta, <span class=\"grc\">ι</span>, pronounced like the \"i\" in <u>ea</u>st.",
						"hintMsg": "<strong>Not Quite.</strong> The correct answer was <strong>\"i\" like <u>ea</u>st</strong>",
						"failureMsg": "<strong>The correct answer was \"i\" like <u>ea</u>st</strong>",
						"require_order": "false",
						"require_all": "true"
					},
					{
						"type": "slide_multi_comp",
						"title": "Identify the letter!",
						"question": "What is the order of these letters in the alphabet?",
						"options": [ [
							{ "value": "λ", "display": "<span lang=\"grc\">λ</span>" },
							{ "value": "ι", "display": "<span lang=\"grc\">ι</span>" },
							{ "value": "κ", "display": "<span lang=\"grc\">κ</span>" },
							{ "value": "θ", "display": "<span lang=\"grc\">θ</span>" }
						]],
						"answers": ["θ", "ι", "κ", "λ"],
						"successMsg": "Correct!",
						"hintMsg": "<strong>Not Quite.</strong> The correct answer was <strong><span lang=\"grc\">θ</span>, <span lang=\"grc\">ι</span>, <span lang=\"grc\">κ</span>, <span lang=\"grc\">λ</span>.</strong>",
						"failureMsg": "<strong>The correct answer was span lang=\"grc\">θ</span>, <span lang=\"grc\">ι</span>, <span lang=\"grc\">κ</span>, <span lang=\"grc\">λ</span>.</strong>",
						"require_order": "true",
						"require_all": "true"
					},
					{
						"type": "slide_info",
						"includeHTML": "/static/content/en/slides/1.alphabet/mu.html"
					},
					{
						"type": "slide_info",
						"includeHTML": "/static/content/en/slides/1.alphabet/nu.html"
					},
					{
						"type": "slide_info",
						"includeHTML": "/static/content/en/slides/1.alphabet/xi.html"
					},
					{
						"type": "slide_info",
						"includeHTML": "/static/content/en/slides/1.alphabet/omicron.html"
					},
					{
						"type": "slide_info",
						"includeHTML": "/static/content/en/slides/1.alphabet/pi.html"
					},
					{
						"type": "slide_info",
						"includeHTML": "/static/content/en/slides/1.alphabet/rho.html"
					},
					{
						"type": "slide_info",
						"includeHTML": "/static/content/en/slides/1.alphabet/sigma.html"
					},
					{
						"type": "slide_info",
						"includeHTML": "/static/content/en/slides/1.alphabet/tau.html"
					},
					{
						"type": "slide_info",
						"includeHTML": "/static/content/en/slides/1.alphabet/upsilon.html"
					},
					{
						"type": "slide_direct_select",
						"settings": { "orientation": "vertical" },
						"title": "Identify the letter!",
						"question": "How does <strong lang=\"grc\">ν</strong> sound and what is it called?",
						"options": [ [
							{ "value": "gamma - gigantic", "display": "Gamma - like <u>g</u>iant" },
							{ "value": "gamma - good", "display": "Gamma - like <u>g</u>ood" },
							{ "value": "üpsilon - food", "display": "Upsilon - like f<u>oo</u>d" },
							{ "value": "nu - nose", "display": "Nu - like <u>n</u>ose" }
						]],
						"answers": ["nu - nose"],
						"successMsg": "<strong>Right Answer!</strong>",
						"hintMsg": "<strong>Not Quite.</strong> Remember that Nu sounds like the <strong>\"n\" in book.</strong>",
						"failureMsg": "<strong>The correct answer was \"n\" like book.</strong>",
						"require_order": "false",
						"require_all": "true"
					},
					{
						"type": "slide_direct_select",
						"settings": { "orientation": "horizontal" },
						"title": "Identify the letter!",
						"question": "Which of these are <strong>rho</strong>?",
						"options": [ [
							{ "value": "τ", "display": "<span lang=\"grc\">τ</span>" },
							{ "value": "Τ", "display": "<span lang=\"grc\">Τ</span>" },
							{ "value": "Ρ", "display": "<span lang=\"grc\">Ρ</span>" },
							{ "value": "ρ", "display": "<span lang=\"grc\">ρ</span>" },
							{ "value": "Π", "display": "<span lang=\"grc\">Π</span>" },
							{ "value": "π", "display": "<span lang=\"grc\">π</span>" }	
						]],
						"answers": ["ρ", "Ρ"],
						"successMsg": "<strong>Right Answer!</strong> You've identified rho, <span class=\"grc\">Ρ ρ</span>, pronounced like the \"r\" in <u>r</u>ose.",
						"hintMsg": "<strong>Not Quite.</strong> The correct answer was <strong><span class=\"grc\">Ρ ρ</span></strong>",
						"failureMsg": "<strong>The correct answer was <span class=\"grc\">Ρ ρ</span></strong>",
						"require_order": "false",
						"require_all": "true"
					},
					{
						"type": "slide_multi_comp",
						"title": "Identify the letter!",
						"question": "What is the order of these letters in the alphabet?",
						"options": [ [
							{ "value": "μ", "display": "<span lang=\"grc\">μ</span>" },
							{ "value": "ο", "display": "<span lang=\"grc\">ο</span>" },
							{ "value": "ν", "display": "<span lang=\"grc\">ν</span>" },
							{ "value": "π", "display": "<span lang=\"grc\">π</span>" }
						]],
						"answers": ["μ", "ν", "ο", "π"],
						"successMsg": "Awesome!",
						"hintMsg": "<strong>Not Quite</strong> The correct answer was <strong><span lang=\"grc\">μ</span>, <span lang=\"grc\">ν</span>, <span lang=\"grc\">ο</span>, <span lang=\"grc\">π</span>.</strong>",
						"failureMsg": "<strong>The correct answer was <span lang=\"grc\">μ</span>, <span lang=\"grc\">ν</span>, <span lang=\"grc\">ο</span>, <span lang=\"grc\">π</span>.</strong>",
						"require_order": "true",
						"require_all": "true"
					},
					{
						"type": "slide_direct_select",
						"settings": { "orientation": "vertical" },
						"title": "Identify the letter!",
						"question": "Which of these are a <strong>sigma</strong>?",
						"options": [ [
							{ "value": "ς", "display": "<span lang=\"grc\">ς</span>" },
							{ "value": "ο", "display": "<span lang=\"grc\">ο</span>" },
							{ "value": "σ", "display": "<span lang=\"grc\">σ</span>" }
						]],
						"answers": ["ς", "σ"],
						"successMsg": "<strong>Right Answer!</strong> You've identified sigma, <span class=\"grc\">σ,ς</span>, pronounced like the \"s\" in <u>s</u>ignal.",
						"hintMsg": "<strong>Not Quite.</strong> The correct answer is <strong>\"s\" like <u>s</u>ignal.</strong>",
						"failureMsg": "<strong>The correct answer was \"s\" like <u>s</u>ignal.</strong>",
						"require_order": "false",
						"require_all": "true"
					},
					{
						"type": "slide_direct_select",
						"settings": { "orientation": "vertical" },
						"title": "Identify the letter!",
						"question": "How does <strong lang=\"grc\">ρ</strong> sound and what is it called?",
						"options": [ [
							{ "value": "rho - rose", "display": "Rho - like <u>r</u>ose" },
							{ "value": "pi - pen", "display": "Pi - like <u>p</u>en" },
							{ "value": "üpsilon - food", "display": "Upsilon - like f<u>oo</u>d" },
							{ "value": "nu - nose", "display": "Nu - like <u>n</u>ose" }
						]],
						"answers": ["rho - rose"],
						"successMsg": "<strong>Right Answer!</strong>",
						"hintMsg": "<strong>Not Quite.</strong> The correct answer was <strong>\"r\" like rose.</strong>",
						"failureMsg": "<strong>The correct answer was \"r\" like rose.</strong>",
						"require_order": "false",
						"require_all": "true"
					},
					{
						"type": "slide_multi_comp",
						"title": "Identify the letter!",
						"question": "What is the order of these letters in the alphabet?",
						"options": [ [
							{ "value": "ρ", "display": "<span lang=\"grc\">ρ</span>" },
							{ "value": "υ", "display": "<span lang=\"grc\">υ</span>" },
							{ "value": "ς", "display": "<span lang=\"grc\">ς</span>" },
							{ "value": "τ", "display": "<span lang=\"grc\">τ</span>" }
						]],
						"answers": ["ρ", "ς", "τ", "υ"],
						"successMsg": "You're awesome!",
						"hintMsg": "<strong>Not Quite.</strong> The correct answer was <strong><span lang=\"grc\">ρ</span>, <span lang=\"grc\">ς</span>, <span lang=\"grc\">τ</span>, <span lang=\"grc\">υ</span>.</strong>",
						"failureMsg": "<strong>The correct answer was <span lang=\"grc\">ρ</span>, <span lang=\"grc\">ς</span>, <span lang=\"grc\">τ</span>, <span lang=\"grc\">υ</span>.</strong>",
						"require_order": "true",
						"require_all": "true"
					},
					{
						"type": "slide_direct_select",
						"settings": { "orientation": "vertical" },
						"title": "Identify the letter!",
						"question": "Which of these is a <strong>tau</strong>?",
						"options": [ [
							{ "value": "ς", "display": "<span lang=\"grc\">ς</span>" },
							{ "value": "ν", "display": "<span lang=\"grc\">ν</span>" },
							{ "value": "τ", "display": "<span lang=\"grc\">τ</span>" }
						]],
						"answers": ["τ"],
						"successMsg": "<strong>Right Answer!</strong> You've identified tau, <span class=\"grc\">τ</span>, pronounced like the \"t\" in <u>t</u>ower.",
						"hintMsg": "<strong>Not Quite.</strong> The correct answer was <strong>\"t\" like <u>t</u>ower.</strong>",
						"failureMsg": "<strong>The correct answer was \"t\" like <u>t</u>ower.</strong>",
						"require_order": "false",
						"require_all": "true"
					},
					{
						"type": "slide_info",
						"includeHTML": "/static/content/en/slides/1.alphabet/phi.html"
					},
					{
						"type": "slide_info",
						"includeHTML": "/static/content/en/slides/1.alphabet/chi.html"
					},
					{
						"type": "slide_info",
						"includeHTML": "/static/content/en/slides/1.alphabet/psi.html"
					},
					{
						"type": "slide_info",
						"includeHTML": "/static/content/en/slides/1.alphabet/omega.html"
					},
					{
						"type": "slide_direct_select",
						"settings": { "orientation": "vertical" },
						"title": "Identify the letter!",
						"question": "How does <strong lang=\"grc\">χ</strong> sound and what is it called?",
						"options": [ [
							{ "value": "kappa - coat", "display": "Kappa - like <u>c</u>oat" },
							{ "value": "khi - kiosk", "display": "Khi - like <u>k</u>iosk" },
							{ "value": "Fi - flower", "display": "Fi - like <u>f</u>lower" },
							{ "value": "Tau - tower", "display": "Tau - like <u>t</u>ower" }
						]],
						"answers": ["khi - kiosk"],
						"successMsg": "<strong>Right Answer!</strong> Remember that Khi sounds like the \"k\" in kiosk.",
						"hintMsg": "<strong>Not Quite.</strong> The correct answer was <strong>\"k\" like kiosk.</strong>",
						"failureMsg": "<strong>The correct answer was \"k\" like kiosk.</strong>",
						"require_order": "false",
						"require_all": "true"
					},
					{
						"type": "slide_direct_select",
						"settings": { "orientation": "vertical" },
						"title": "Identify the letter!",
						"question": "Which of these is a <strong>Phi</strong>?",
						"options": [ [
							{ "value": "φ", "display": "<span lang=\"grc\">φ</span>" },
							{ "value": "ψ", "display": "<span lang=\"grc\">ψ</span>" },
							{ "value": "χ", "display": "<span lang=\"grc\">χ</span>" }
						]],
						"answers": ["φ"],
						"successMsg": "<strong>Right Answer!</strong> You've identified fi, <span class=\"grc\">φ</span>, pronounced like the \"f\" in <u>f</u>lower.",
						"hintMsg": "<strong>Not Quite.</strong> The correct answer was <strong>\"f\" like <u>f</u>lower.</strong>",
						"failureMsg": "<strong>The correct answer was \"f\" like <u>f</u>lower.</strong>",
						"require_order": "false",
						"require_all": "true"
					},
					{
						"type": "slide_direct_select",
						"settings": { "orientation": "horizontal" },
						"title": "Identify the letter!",
						"question": "Which of these are <strong>omega</strong>?",
						"options": [ [
							{ "value": "Φ", "display": "<span lang=\"grc\">Φ</span>" },
							{ "value": "φ", "display": "<span lang=\"grc\">φ</span>" },
							{ "value": "Χ", "display": "<span lang=\"grc\">Χ</span>" },
							{ "value": "χ", "display": "<span lang=\"grc\">χ</span>" },
							{ "value": "ω", "display": "<span lang=\"grc\">ω</span>" },
							{ "value": "Ω", "display": "<span lang=\"grc\">Ω</span>" }	
						]],
						"answers": ["ω", "Ω"],
						"successMsg": "<strong>Right Answer!</strong> You've identified omega, <span class=\"grc\">Ω ω</span>, pronounced like the \"o\" in <u>o</u>strich.",
						"hintMsg": "<strong>Not Quite.</strong> The correct answer was <strong>\"ω\", \"Ω\".</strong>",
						"failureMsg": "<strong>The correct answer was \"ω\", \"Ω\".</strong>",
						"require_order": "false",
						"require_all": "true"
					},
					{
						"type": "slide_multi_comp",
						"title": "Identify the letter!",
						"question": "What is the order of these letters in the alphabet?",
						"options": [ [
							{ "value": "ψ", "display": "<span lang=\"grc\">ψ</span>" },
							{ "value": "χ", "display": "<span lang=\"grc\">χ</span>" },
							{ "value": "φ", "display": "<span lang=\"grc\">φ</span>" },
							{ "value": "ω", "display": "<span lang=\"grc\">ω</span>" }
						]],
						"answers": ["φ", "χ", "ψ", "ω"],
						"successMsg": "You're awesome!",
						"hintMsg": "<strong>Not Quite.</strong> The correct answer was <strong><span lang=\"grc\">φ</span>, <span lang=\"grc\">χ</span>, <span lang=\"grc\">ψ</span>, <span lang=\"grc\">ω</span>.</strong>",
						"failureMsg": "<strong>The correct answer was <span lang=\"grc\">φ</span>, <span lang=\"grc\">χ</span>, <span lang=\"grc\">ψ</span>, <span lang=\"grc\">ω</span>.</strong>",
						"require_order": "true",
						"require_all": "true"
					},
					{	
						"type": "slide_info",
						"includeHTML": "/static/content/en/slides/1.alphabet/alphabettable.html",
						"smyth": "s1"
					},
					{	
						"type": "slide_info",
						"includeHTML": "/static/content/en/slides/1.alphabet/excep.html",
						"smyth": "s19#a"
					},
					{	
						"type": "slide_info",
						"includeHTML": "/static/content/en/slides/1.alphabet/punctuation.html",
						"smyth": "s188"
					},
					{	
						"type": "slide_info",
						"includeHTML": "/static/content/en/slides/1.alphabet/concl.html"
					}
				]
			}
		]
	},
	{
		"title": "Diacritics & Dipthongs",
		"modules": [
			{	"title": "Diacritics and Dipthongs",
				"slides": [
					{	
						"type": "slide_info",
						"includeHTML": "/static/content/en/slides/2.diacritics/intro.html"
					},
					{	
						"type": "slide_info",
						"includeHTML": "/static/content/en/slides/2.diacritics/rough.html",
						"smyth": "s9"
					},
					{
						"type": "slide_direct_select",
						"settings": { "orientation": "vertical" },
						"title": "Pronounciation Challenge!",
						"question": "How would you pronounce <span lang=\"grc\">ὁδός</span>, <em>way</em>?",
						"options": [ [
							{ "value": "Oh-dos", "display": "Oh-dos" },
							{ "value": "Hoh-dos", "display": "Hoh-dos" },
							{ "value": "Roh-dos", "display": "Roh-dos" }
						]],
						"answers": ["Hoh-dos"],
						"successMsg": "<strong>Right Answer!</strong> You remembered that <span lang=\"grc\">ὁ</span> is pronounced like \"hoh\".",
						"hintMsg": "<strong>Not Quite</strong> Remember that <span lang=\"grc\">ὁ</span> is pronounced like \"hoh\" because of the rough breathing.",
						"failureMsg": "<strong>The correct answer was...</strong>",
						"require_order": "false",
						"require_all": "true"
					},
					{
						"type": "slide_direct_select",
						"settings": { "orientation": "vertical" },
						"title": "Pronounciation Challenge!",
						"question": "How would you spell <strong>Hellēnes</strong>, <em>Greeks</em>?",
						"options": [ [
							{ "value": "´Ελληνες", "display": "<span lang=\"grc\">´Ελληνες</span>" },
							{ "value": "`Ελληνες", "display": "<span lang=\"grc\">`Ελληνες</span>" },
							{ "value": "῾´Ελληνες", "display": "<span lang=\"grc\">῾´Ελληνες</span>" }
						]],
						"answers": ["῾´Ελληνες"],
						"successMsg": "<strong>Right Answer!</strong> You remembered that the He sound must come from a rough breathing, such as <span lang=\"grc\">῾´Ε</span>.",
						"hintMsg": "<strong>Not Quite</strong> Remember that in Greek, the H sound must come from a rough breathing, such as <span lang=\"grc\">῾´Ε</span>.",
						"failureMsg": "<strong>The correct answer was...</strong>",
						"require_order": "false",
						"require_all": "true"
					},
					{	
						"type": "slide_info",
						"includeHTML": "/static/content/en/slides/2.diacritics/smooth.html",
						"smyth": "s9"
					},
					{
						"type": "slide_direct_select",
						"settings": { "orientation": "vertical" },
						"title": "Pronounciation Challenge!",
						"question": "How would you pronounce <span lang=\"grc\">ὀλιγαρχία</span>, <em>oligarchy</em>?",
						"options": [ [
							{ "value": "Roh-li-gar-khia", "display": "Roh-li-gar-khia" },
							{ "value": "Hoh-li-gar-khia", "display": "Hoh-li-gar-khia" },
							{ "value": "Oh-li-gar-khia", "display": "Oh-li-gar-khia" }
						]],
						"answers": ["Oh-li-gar-khia"],
						"successMsg": "<strong>Right Answer!</strong> You remembered that <span lang=\"grc\">ὀ</span> sounds like 'oh', because of its smooth breathing.",
						"hintMsg": "<strong>Not Quite</strong> Remember that smooth breathings don't affect pronunciation. So <span lang=\"grc\">ὀλιγαρχία</span> simply sounds like 'Oh-li-gar-khia'.",
						"failureMsg": "<strong>The correct answer was...</strong>",
						"require_order": "false",
						"require_all": "true"
					},
					{	
						"type": "slide_info",
						"includeHTML": "/static/content/en/slides/2.diacritics/longshort.html",
						"smyth": "s4"
					},
					{
						"type": "slide_direct_select",
						"settings": { "orientation": "horizontal" },
						"title": "What is the long version of <span lang=\"grc\">ε</span>, epsilon?",
						"question": "What is the long version of <span lang=\"grc\">ε</span>, epsilon?",
						"options": [ [
							{ "value": "η", "display": "<span lang=\"grc\">η</span>" },
							{ "value": "υ", "display": "<span lang=\"grc\">υ</span>" },
							{ "value": "ω", "display": "<span lang=\"grc\">ω</span>" }
						]],
						"answers": ["η"],
						"successMsg": "<strong>Right Answer!</strong> You remembered that <span lang=\"grc\">η</span>, eta, is the long version of <span lang=\"grc\">ε</span>, epsilon.",
						"hintMsg": "<strong>Not Quite</strong> Remember that <span lang=\"grc\">η</span>, eta, is the long version of <span lang=\"grc\">ε</span>, epsilon.",
						"failureMsg": "<strong>The correct answer was...</strong>",
						"require_order": "false",
						"require_all": "true"
					},
					{
						"type": "slide_direct_select",
						"settings": { "orientation": "horizontal" },
						"title": "Vowel Lengths!",
						"question": "Which of these vowels can NOT be <strong>long</strong>?",
						"options": [ [
							{ "value": "α", "display": "<span lang=\"grc\">α</span>" },
							{ "value": "ε", "display": "<span lang=\"grc\">ε</span>" },
							{ "value": "η", "display": "<span lang=\"grc\">η</span>" },
							{ "value": "ι", "display": "<span lang=\"grc\">ι</span>" },
							{ "value": "ο", "display": "<span lang=\"grc\">ο</span>" },
							{ "value": "ω", "display": "<span lang=\"grc\">ω</span>" },
							{ "value": "υ", "display": "<span lang=\"grc\">υ</span>" }
						]],
						"answers": ["α", "ε", "υ", "ο", "ι"],
						"successMsg": "<strong>Right Answer!</strong> These are all vowels that are either short, or can be short or long.",
						"hintMsg": "<strong>Not Quite</strong> Remember that <span lang=\"grc\">ω</span> and <span lang=\"grc\">η</span> can only be long vowels. The short vowels are <span lang=\"grc\">α, ε, ι, ο, υ</span>.",
						"failureMsg": "<strong>The correct answer was...</strong>",
						"require_order": "false",
						"require_all": "true"
					},
					{
						"type": "slide_direct_select",
						"settings": { "orientation": "horizontal" },
						"title": "Vowel Lengths!",
						"question": "Which of these vowels MUST be <strong>long</strong>?",
						"options": [ [
							{ "value": "α", "display": "<span lang=\"grc\">α</span>" },
							{ "value": "ε", "display": "<span lang=\"grc\">ε</span>" },
							{ "value": "η", "display": "<span lang=\"grc\">η</span>" },
							{ "value": "ι", "display": "<span lang=\"grc\">ι</span>" },
							{ "value": "ο", "display": "<span lang=\"grc\">ο</span>" },
							{ "value": "ω", "display": "<span lang=\"grc\">ω</span>" },
							{ "value": "υ", "display": "<span lang=\"grc\">υ</span>" }
						]],
						"answers": ["η", "ω"],
						"successMsg": "<strong>Right Answer!</strong> These are all vowels that must be long.",
						"hintMsg": "<strong>Not Quite</strong> Remember that <span lang=\"grc\">ω</span> and <span lang=\"grc\">η</span> can only be long vowels. The short vowels are <span lang=\"grc\">α, ε, ι, ο, υ</span>.",
						"failureMsg": "<strong>The correct answer was...</strong>",
						"require_order": "false",
						"require_all": "true"
					},
					{	
						"type": "slide_info",
						"includeHTML": "/static/content/en/slides/2.diacritics/iota.html",
						"smyth": "s5"
					},
					{	
						"type": "slide_info",
						"includeHTML": "/static/content/en/slides/2.diacritics/accents.html"
					},
					{
						"type": "slide_direct_select",
						"settings": { "orientation": "vertical" },
						"title": "Accents",
						"question": "Which of these words contains an <strong>acute</strong> accent?",
						"options": [ [
							{ "value": "ὁδός (way)", "display": "<span lang=\"grc\">ὁδός</span> (way)" },
							{ "value": "σῶμα (body)", "display": "<span lang=\"grc\">σῶμα</span> (body)" },
							{ "value": "ὑπὸ (by)", "display": "<span lang=\"grc\">ὑπὸ ...</span> (by)" }
						]],
						"answers": ["ὁδός (way)"],
						"successMsg": "<strong>Right Answer!</strong> The <span lang=\"grc\">ό</span> in <span lang=\"grc\">ὁδός</span> has an acute accent.",
						"hintMsg": "<strong>Not Quite</strong> Remember, the acute accent points right: ´ .",
						"failureMsg": "<strong>The correct answer was...</strong>",
						"require_order": "false",
						"require_all": "true"
					},
					{
						"type": "slide_direct_select",
						"settings": { "orientation": "vertical" },
						"title": "Accents",
						"question": "Which of these words contains a <strong>circumflex</strong> accent?",
						"options": [ [
							{ "value": "ὁδός (way)", "display": "<span lang=\"grc\">ὁδός</span> (way)" },
							{ "value": "σῶμα (body)", "display": "<span lang=\"grc\">σῶμα</span> (body)" },
							{ "value": "ὑπὸ (by)", "display": "<span lang=\"grc\">ὑπὸ ...</span> (by)" }
						]],
						"answers": ["σῶμα (body)"],
						"successMsg": "<strong>Right Answer!</strong> The <span lang=\"grc\">ῶ</span> in <span lang=\"grc\">σῶμα</span> has a circumflex accent.",
						"hintMsg": "<strong>Not Quite</strong> Remember, the circumflex is crazy and wavy: ῀",
						"failureMsg": "<strong>The correct answer was...</strong>",
						"require_order": "false",
						"require_all": "true"
					},
					{
						"type": "slide_direct_select",
						"settings": { "orientation": "vertical" },
						"title": "Accents",
						"question": "Which of these words contains a <strong>grave</strong> accent?",
						"options": [ [
							{ "value": "ὁδός (way)", "display": "<span lang=\"grc\">ὁδός</span> (way)" },
							{ "value": "σῶμα (body)", "display": "<span lang=\"grc\">σῶμα</span> (body)" },
							{ "value": "ὑπὸ (by)", "display": "<span lang=\"grc\">ὑπὸ ...</span> (by)" }
						]],
						"answers": ["ὑπὸ (by)"],
						"successMsg": "<strong>Right Answer!</strong> The <span lang=\"grc\">ὸ</span> in <span lang=\"grc\">ὑπὸ</span> has a grave accent.",
						"hintMsg": "<strong>Not Quite</strong> Remember, the grave accent points to the left: `",
						"failureMsg": "<strong>The correct answer was...</strong>",
						"require_order": "false",
						"require_all": "true"
					},
					{	
						"type": "slide_info",
						"includeHTML": "/static/content/en/slides/2.diacritics/general.html",
						"smyth": "s149"
					},
					{	
						"type": "slide_info",
						"includeHTML": "/static/content/en/slides/2.diacritics/acute.html"
					},
					{	
						"type": "slide_info",
						"includeHTML": "/static/content/en/slides/2.diacritics/grave.html"
					},
					{	
						"type": "slide_info",
						"includeHTML": "/static/content/en/slides/2.diacritics/circumflex.html"
					},
					{	
						"type": "slide_info",
						"includeHTML": "/static/content/en/slides/2.diacritics/dipthongs.html"
					},
					{	
						"type": "slide_info",
						"includeHTML": "/static/content/en/slides/2.diacritics/concl.html"
					}
				]
			}
		]
	},
	{
		"title": "Introduction to Nouns",
		"modules": [
			{
				"title": "Nouns in Ancient Greek",
				"slides": [
					{
						"type": "slide_info",
						"includeHTML": "/static/content/en/slides/3.nouns/intro.html"
					},
					{
						"type": "slide_info",
						"includeHTML": "/static/content/en/slides/3.nouns/history.html"
					},
					{
						"type": "slide_info",
						"includeHTML": "/static/content/en/slides/3.nouns/nouns.html",
						"smyth": "s194"
					},	
					{
						"type": "slide_info",
						"includeHTML": "/static/content/en/slides/3.nouns/nouns1.html",
						"smyth": "s194"
					},
					{
						"type": "slide_direct_select",
						"settings": {
							"orientation": "vertical"
						},
						"title": "Know your Greek!",
						"question": "Select all the characteristics of a <strong>Noun</strong> in Ancient Greek.",
						"options": [[
								{ "value": "Gender", "display": "Gender" },
								{ "value": "Tense", "display": "Tense" },
								{ "value": "Number", "display": "Number" },
								{ "value": "Person", "display": "Person" },
								{ "value": "Case", "display": "Case" }
						]],
						"answers": ["Gender", "Number", "Case"],
						"successMsg": "<strong>Right Answer!</strong> When you see a noun, you'll need to figure out these three characteristics.",
						"hintMsg": "<strong>Not Quite</strong> Nouns in Greek have three characteristics: Gender, Number, and Case.",
						"failureMsg": "<strong>The correct answer was...</strong>",
						"require_order": "false",
						"require_all": "true"
					},
					{
						"type": "slide_info",
						"includeHTML": "/static/content/en/slides/3.nouns/characteristics.html",
						"smyth": "s194"
					},
					{
						"type": "slide_info",
						"includeHTML": "/static/content/en/slides/3.nouns/gender.html",
						"smyth": "s196"
					},
					{
						"type": "slide_direct_select",
						"settings": {
							"orientation": "vertical"
						},
						"title": "Exercise: Pick the correct definite article",
						"question": "Which definite article (\"the\") corresponds to <strong>feminine nouns</strong>, such as <span lang=\"grc\" class=\"fem\">ἡμέρα</span> (day)?",
						"options": [[
								{ "value": "ὁ", "display": "<span lang=\"grc\">ὁ</span>" },
								{ "value": "ἡ", "display": "<span lang=\"grc\">ἡ</span>" },
								{ "value": "τό", "display": "<span lang=\"grc\">τό</span>" }
						]],
						"answers": ["ἡ"],
						"successMsg": "<strong>Right Answer!</strong> The definite article for feminine nouns like <span lang=\"grc\">ἡμέρα</span> is <span lang=\"grc\">ἡ</span>.",
						"hintMsg": "<strong>Not Quite</strong>",
						"failureMsg": "<strong>The correct answer was...</strong>",
						"require_order": "false",
						"require_all": "true"
					},
					{
						"type": "slide_direct_select",
						"settings": {
							"orientation": "vertical"
						},
						"title": "Exercise: Pick the correct definite article",
						"question": "Which definite article (\"the\") corresponds to <strong>masculine nouns</strong>, such as <span lang=\"grc\" class=\"masc\">πόλεμος</span> (battle)?",
						"options": [[
								{ "value": "ὁ", "display": "<span lang=\"grc\">ὁ</span>" },
								{ "value": "ἡ", "display": "<span lang=\"grc\">ἡ</span>" },
								{ "value": "τό", "display": "<span lang=\"grc\">τό</span>" }
						]],
						"answers": ["ὁ"],
						"successMsg": "<strong>Right Answer!</strong> The definite article for masculine nouns like <span lang=\"grc\" class=\"masc\">πόλεμος</span> is <span lang=\"grc\">ὁ</span>.",
						"hintMsg": "<strong>Not Quite</strong>",
						"require_order": "false",
						"require_all": "true"
					},
					{
						"type": "slide_direct_select",
						"settings": {
							"orientation": "vertical"
						},
						"title": "Exercise: Pick the correct definite article",
						"question": "Which definite article (\"the\") corresponds to <strong>neuter nouns</strong>, such as <span lang=\"grc\" class=\"neut\">ἔργον</span> (work)?",
						"options": [ [
								{ "value": "ὁ", "display": "<span lang=\"grc\">ὁ</span>" },
								{ "value": "ἡ", "display": "<span lang=\"grc\">ἡ</span>" },
								{ "value": "τό", "display": "<span lang=\"grc\">τό</span>" }
						]],
						"answers": ["τό"],
						"successMsg": "<strong>Right Answer!</strong> The definite article for neuter nouns like <span lang=\"grc\">ἔργον</span> is <span lang=\"grc\">τό</span>.",
						"hintMsg": "<strong>Not Quite</strong>",
						"require_order": "false",
						"require_all": "true"
					},
					{
						"type": "slide_info",
						"includeHTML": "/static/content/en/slides/3.nouns/number.html",
						"smyth": "s195"
					},
					{
						"type": "slide_direct_select",
						"settings": {
							"orientation": "vertical"
						},
						"title": "Know your Greek!",
						"question": "Which definite article (\"the\") agrees with <strong>plural, feminine</strong> nouns like <span lang=\"grc\" class=\"fem\">ἡμέραι</span> (\"days\")?",
						"options": [[
								{ "value": "τά", "display": "<span lang=\"grc\">τά</span>" },
								{ "value": "ἡ", "display": "<span lang=\"grc\">ἡ</span>" },
								{ "value": "αἱ", "display": "<span lang=\"grc\">αἱ</span>" }
						]],
						"answers": ["αἱ"],
						"successMsg": "<strong>Right Answer!</strong> You noticed that the ending of the article and the noun itself match!",
						"hintMsg": "<strong>Not Quite</strong> Look at the endings and see how they're similar: <span lang=\"grc\"><em>αἱ</em> ἡμέρ<em>αι</em></span> (\"the days\").",
						"failureMsg": "<strong>The correct answer was...</strong>",
						"require_order": "false",
						"require_all": "true"
					},
					{
						"type": "slide_info",
						"includeHTML": "/static/content/en/slides/3.nouns/case.html"
					},
					{
						"type": "slide_info",
						"includeHTML": "/static/content/en/slides/3.nouns/articles.html",
						"smyth": "s332"
					},
					{
						"type": "slide_info",
						"includeHTML": "/static/content/en/slides/3.nouns/treebank-nouns.html"
					},
					{
						"type": "slide_info",
						"includeHTML": "/static/content/en/slides/3.nouns/treebank-exercises.html"
					},
					{
						"type": "slide_info",
						"includeHTML": "/static/content/en/slides/3.nouns/nouns_concl.html"
					}
				]
			}
		]
	},
	{
		"title": "Introduction to Cases",
		"modules": [
			{
				"title": "Nominative Case",
				"slides": [
					{
						"type": "slide_info",
						"includeHTML": "/static/content/en/slides/4.cases/intro.html"
					},
					{
						"type": "slide_info",
						"includeHTML": "/static/content/en/slides/4.cases/history.html"
					},
					{
						"type": "slide_info",
						"includeHTML": "/static/content/en/slides/4.cases/nominative.html"
					},
					{
						"type": "slide_info",
						"includeHTML": "/static/content/en/slides/4.cases/nominative_subj.html"
					},
					{
						"type": "slide_info",
						"includeHTML": "/static/content/en/slides/4.cases/nominative_comp.html"
					},
					{
						"type": "slide_direct_select",
						"settings": 
							{ 
								"orientation" : "horizontal" 
							},
						"title": "Exercise: Select the Subject of this Sentence",
						"question": "Which of these words is the subject of the following English sentence:",
						"options": [
							[
								{
									"value": "The ships",
									"display": "The ships"
								},
								{
									"value": "sailed",
									"display": "sailed"
								},
								{
									"value": "to Sicily",
									"display": "to Sicily"
								}
							]
						],
						"answers": ["The ships"],
						"successMsg": "<strong>Right Answer!</strong> \"The Ships\" is the subject of this sentence, because it performs the action of the verb, \"sailed\". If this sentence were in Greek, \"The ships\" would be in the <strong>nominative case</strong>.", 
						"hintMsg": "<strong>Not quite.</strong>",
						"require_order": "false",
						"require_all": "true"
					},
					{
						"type": "slide_direct_select",
						"settings": 
							{ 
								"orientation" : "horizontal" 
							},
						"title": "Exercise: Select the <strong>Complement</strong> of this Sentence",
						"question": "Which of these words is the complement to the subject?",
						"options": [
							[
								{
									"value": "The day",
									"display": "<span lang=\"grc\">ἡ ἡμέρα</span><br><small>The day</small>"
								},
								{
									"value": "is",
									"display": "<span lang=\"grc\">ἐστὶ</span><br><small>is</small>"
								},
								{
									"value": "long",
									"display": "<span lang=\"grc\">μακρά</span><br><small>long</small>"
								}
							]
						],
						"answers": ["long"],
						"successMsg": "<strong>Right Answer!</strong> You noticed that 'long' is the complement to the subject, 'the day'.", 
						"hintMsg": "<strong>Not quite.</strong>",
						"require_order": "false",
						"require_all": "true"
					},
					{
						"type": "slide_direct_select",
						"settings": 
							{ 
								"orientation" : "vertical" 
							},
						"title": "Exercise: Pick the Correct Case",
						"question": "In which case does the <strong>subject of a sentence</strong> belong?",
						"options": [
							[
								{
									"value": "Nominative",
									"display": "Nominative"
								},
								{
									"value": "Genitive",
									"display": "Genitive"
								},
								{
									"value": "Dative",
									"display": "Dative"
								}
							]
						],
						"answers": ["Nominative"],
						"successMsg": "<strong>Right Answer!</strong> Subjects of a sentence always belong in the nominative case.", 
						"hintMsg": "<strong>Not quite.</strong>",
						"require_order": "false",
						"require_all": "true"
					},
					{
						"type": "slide_info",
						"includeHTML": "/static/content/en/slides/4.cases/nominative_pent.html"
					},
					{
						"type": "slide_info",
						"includeHTML": "/static/content/en/slides/4.cases/nominative_concl.html"
					}
				]
			},
			{
				"title": "Accusative Case",
				"slides": [
					{	
						"type": "slide_info",
						"includeHTML": "/static/content/en/slides/4.cases/accusative.html"
					},
					{
						"type": "slide_direct_select",
						"settings": {
							"orientation": "horizontal"
						},
						"title": "Exercise: Select the Direct Object",
						"question": "In the following sentence, which word or words are the direct object, and would belong in the <strong>accusative case</strong> if they were written in Greek?",
						"options": [
							[
								{
									"value": "The king",
									"display": "The king"
								},
								{  
									"value": "gave",
									"display": "gave"
								},
								{
									"value": "an order",
									"display": "an order"
								}
							]
						],
						"answers": ["an order"],
						"successMsg": "<strong>Right Answer!</strong>",
						"hintMsg": "<strong>Not Quite</strong>",
						"failureMsg": "<strong>The correct answer was...</strong>",
						"require_order": "false",
						"require_all": "true"
					},
					{
						"type": "slide_direct_select",
						"settings": 
							{ 
								"orientation" : "horizontal" 
							},
						"title": "Exercise: Select the Direct Object",
						"question": "Which of these words is in the accusative case?",
						"options": [
							[
								{
									"value": "The city",
									"display": "ἡ πόλις<br><small>The city</small>"
								},
								{
									"value": "has",
									"display": "ἔχει<br><small>has</small>"
								},
								{
									"value": "an army",
									"display": "στρατίαν<br><small>an army</small>"
								}
							]
						],
						"answers": ["an army"],
						"successMsg": "<strong>Right Answer!</strong>", 
						"hintMsg": "<strong>Not quite.</strong>",
						"require_order": "false",
						"require_all": "true"
					},
					{	
						"type": "slide_info",
						"includeHTML": "/static/content/en/slides/4.cases/accusative_pent.html"
					},
					{
						"type": "slide_info",
						"includeHTML": "/static/content/en/slides/4.cases/accusative_concl.html"
					}
				]
			},
			{
				"title": "Genitive Case",
				"slides": [
					{
						"type": "slide_info",
						"includeHTML": "/static/content/en/slides/4.cases/genitive.html"
					},
					{
						"type": "slide_info",
						"includeHTML": "/static/content/en/slides/4.cases/genitive_poss.html"
					},
					{
						"type": "slide_info",
						"includeHTML": "/static/content/en/slides/4.cases/genitive_part.html"
					},
					{
						"type": "slide_info",
						"includeHTML": "/static/content/en/slides/4.cases/genitive_comp.html"
					},
					{
						"type": "slide_info",
						"includeHTML": "/static/content/en/slides/4.cases/genitive_pent.html"
					},
					{
						"type": "slide_info",
						"includeHTML": "/static/content/en/slides/4.cases/genitive_concl.html"
					}
				]
			},
			{
				"title": "Dative Case",
				"slides": [
					{
						"type": "slide_info",
						"includeHTML": "/static/content/en/slides/4.cases/dative.html"
					},
					{
						"type": "slide_info",
						"includeHTML": "/static/content/en/slides/4.cases/dative_in.html"
					},
					{
						"type": "slide_info",
						"includeHTML": "/static/content/en/slides/4.cases/dative_pent.html"
					},
					{
						"type": "slide_info",
						"includeHTML": "/static/content/en/slides/4.cases/dative_concl.html"
					}
				]
			},
			{
				"title": "Vocative Case",
				"slides": [
					{
						"type": "slide_info",
						"includeHTML": "/static/content/en/slides/4.cases/vocative.html"
					},
					{
						"type": "slide_info",
						"includeHTML": "/static/content/en/slides/4.cases/vocative_concl.html"
					}
				]
			},
			{
				"title": "Placeholder",
				"slides" : [
					{
						"type": "slide_multi_composition",
						"title": "Make the forms agree!",
						"question": "What is the accusative plural form for \"the small country\"?",
						"options": [
							[
								{
									"value": "τῆς",
									"display": "τῆς"
								},
								{  
									"value": "ἡ",
									"display": "ἡ"
								},
								{
									"value": "τὰς",
									"display": "τὰς"
								}
							],
							[
								{
									"value": "μῑκρᾷ",
									"display": "μῑκρᾷ"
								},
								{  
									"value": "μῑκραὶ",
									"display": "μῑκραὶ"
								},
								{
									"value": "μῑκρὰς",
									"display": "μῑκρὰς"
								}
							],
							[
								{
									"value": "χώρᾱν",
									"display": "χώρᾱν"
								},
								{  
									"value": "χώραιν",
									"display": "χώραιν"
								},
								{
									"value": "χώρᾱς",
									"display": "χώρᾱς"
								}
							]
						],
						"answers": ["τὰς", "μῑκρὰς", "χώρᾱς"],
						"successMsg": "<strong>Right Answer!</strong> The accusative plural form of 'the small country' is <span lang=\"grc\">τὰς μῑκρὰς χώρᾱς</span>.",
						"hintMsg": "<strong>Not Quite</strong>",
						"failureMsg": "<strong>The correct answer was...</strong>",
						"require_order": "true",
						"require_all": "true"
					}
				]
			}
		]
	},
	{
		"title": "First or α- Declension",
		"modules": [
			{
				"title": "The First or α- Declension",
				"slides": [
					{
						"type": "slide_info",
						"includeHTML": "/static/content/en/slides/5.firstdec/intro.html"
					},
					{
						"type": "slide_info",
						"includeHTML": "/static/content/en/slides/5.firstdec/history.html"
					},
					{
						"type": "slide_info",
						"includeHTML": "/static/content/en/slides/5.firstdec/firstdec0.html",
						"smyth": "s216"
					},
					{
						"type": "slide_info",
						"includeHTML": "/static/content/en/slides/5.firstdec/firstdec.html",
						"smyth": "s217#a"
					},
					{
						"type": "slide_info",
						"includeHTML": "/static/content/en/slides/5.firstdec/firstdec1.html",
						"smyth": "s217#c"
					},
					{
						"type": "slide_info",
						"includeHTML": "/static/content/en/slides/5.firstdec/firstdec2.html",
						"smyth": "s222"
					},
					{
						"type": "slide_info",
						"includeHTML": "/static/content/en/slides/5.firstdec/firstdec_pent.html"
					},
					{
						"type": "slide_info",
						"includeHTML": "/static/content/en/slides/5.firstdec/firstdec_pent1.html"
					},
					{
						"type": "slide_info",
						"includeHTML": "/static/content/en/slides/5.firstdec/firstdec_concl.html"
					}
				]
			}
		]
	},
	{	
		"title": "Second Declension",
		"modules": [
			{
				"title": "The Second Declension",
				"slides": [
					{
						"type": "slide_info",
						"includeHTML": "/static/content/en/slides/6.seconddec/intro.html"
					},
					{
						"type": "slide_info",
						"includeHTML": "/static/content/en/slides/6.seconddec/history.html"
					},
					{
						"type": "slide_info",
						"includeHTML": "/static/content/en/slides/6.seconddec/seconddec.html",
						"smyth": "s228#a"
					},
					{
						"type": "slide_info",
						"includeHTML": "/static/content/en/slides/6.seconddec/seconddec1.html",
						"smyth": "s228#b"
					},
					{
						"type": "slide_info",
						"includeHTML": "/static/content/en/slides/6.seconddec/seconddec_pent.html"
					},
					{
						"type": "slide_info",
						"includeHTML": "/static/content/en/slides/6.seconddec/seconddec_concl.html"
					}
				]
			}
		]		
	},
	{	
		"title": "Introduction to Verbs",
		"modules": [
			{
				"title": "Verbs in Ancient Greek",
				"slides": [
					{
						"type": "slide_info",
						"includeHTML": "/static/content/en/slides/7.verbs/intro.html"
					},
					{
						"type": "slide_info",
						"includeHTML": "/static/content/en/slides/7.verbs/history.html"
					},
					{
						"type": "slide_info",
						"includeHTML": "/static/content/en/slides/7.verbs/verbs.html"
					},
					{
						"type": "slide_info",
						"includeHTML": "/static/content/en/slides/7.verbs/person.html"
					},
					{
						"type": "slide_info",
						"includeHTML": "/static/content/en/slides/7.verbs/number.html"
					},
					{
						"type": "slide_info",
						"includeHTML": "/static/content/en/slides/7.verbs/tense.html"
					},
					{
						"type": "slide_info",
						"includeHTML": "/static/content/en/slides/7.verbs/mood.html"
					},
					{
						"type": "slide_info",
						"includeHTML": "/static/content/en/slides/7.verbs/voice.html"
					},
					{
						"type": "slide_info",
						"includeHTML": "/static/content/en/slides/7.verbs/concl.html"
					}
				]
			}	
		]
	},
	{	
		"title": "Present Indicative Active",
		"modules": [
			{
				"title": "Present Indicative Active",
				"vocab": [""],
				"slides": [
					{
						"type": "slide_info",
						"includeHTML": "/static/content/en/slides/8.presentindicativeactive/intro.html"
					},
					{
						"type": "slide_info",
						"includeHTML": "/static/content/en/slides/8.presentindicativeactive/history.html"
					},
					{
						"type": "slide_info",
						"includeHTML": "/static/content/en/slides/8.presentindicativeactive/presindact.html"
					},
					{
						"type": "slide_info",
						"includeHTML": "/static/content/en/slides/8.presentindicativeactive/presindact1.html",
						"smyth": "s499",
						"tasks": ["identify_morph_person", "identify_morph_number"]
					},
					{
						"type": "slide_info",
						"includeHTML": "/static/content/en/slides/8.presentindicativeactive/presindact2.html",
						"smyth": "s768#a",
						"tasks": ["identify_morph_person", "identify_morph_number"]
					},
					{
						"type": "slide_info",
						"includeHTML": "/static/content/en/slides/8.presentindicativeactive/presindact_pent.html"
					},
					{
						"type": "slide_info",
						"includeHTML": "/static/content/en/slides/8.presentindicativeactive/concl.html"
					}
				]
			}	
		]
	},
	{	
		"title": "Future Indicative Active",
		"modules": [
			{
				"title": "Form the Future, Indicative, Active for Regular Verbs",
				"slides": [
					{
						"title": "Introduction to Future Indicative Active",
						"type": "slide_info",
						"includeHTML": "/static/content/en/slides/9.futureindicativeactive/intro.html"
					},
					{
						"type": "slide_info",
						"includeHTML": "/static/content/en/slides/9.futureindicativeactive/history.html"
					},
					{
						"title": "What do 'future', 'active', and 'indicative' imply?",
						"type": "slide_info",
						"includeHTML": "/static/content/en/slides/9.futureindicativeactive/futindact.html"
					},
					{
						"title": "Future Indicative Active of λύω",
						"type": "slide_info",
						"includeHTML": "/static/content/en/slides/9.futureindicativeactive/futindact1.html",
						"smyth": "s532",
						"tasks": ["identify_morph_person", "identify_morph_number"]
					},
					{
						"title": "Forming the Future Active Indicative for Stop Verbs",
						"type": "slide_info",
						"includeHTML": "/static/content/en/slides/9.futureindicativeactive/futindact2.html",
						"smyth": "s537",
						"tasks": ["identify_morph_person", "identify_morph_number"]
					},
					{
						"title": "Future Active Indicative of εἰμί",
						"type": "slide_info",
						"includeHTML": "/static/content/en/slides/9.futureindicativeactive/futindact3.html",
						"smyth": "s768#b",
						"tasks": ["identify_morph_person", "identify_morph_number"]
					},
					{
						"title": "The Future Indicative Active in the Pentecontaetia",
						"type": "slide_info",
						"includeHTML": "/static/content/en/slides/9.futureindicativeactive/futindact_pent.html"
					},
					{
						"type": "slide_info",
						"includeHTML": "/static/content/en/slides/9.futureindicativeactive/concl.html"
					}
				]
			}	
		]
	},
	{	
		"title": "Adjectives: First and Second Declension",
		"modules": [
			{
				"title": "Adjectives: First and Second Declension",
				"slides": [
					{
						"type": "slide_info",
						"includeHTML": "/static/content/en/slides/10.adjectivesfirsec/intro.html"
					},
					{
						"type": "slide_info",
						"includeHTML": "/static/content/en/slides/10.adjectivesfirsec/history.html"
					},
					{
						"type": "slide_info",
						"includeHTML": "/static/content/en/slides/10.adjectivesfirsec/adjectives.html"
					},
					{
						"type": "slide_info",
						"includeHTML": "/static/content/en/slides/10.adjectivesfirsec/3ending.html"
					},
					{
						"type": "slide_info",
						"includeHTML": "/static/content/en/slides/10.adjectivesfirsec/2ending.html"
					},
					{
						"type": "slide_info",
						"includeHTML": "/static/content/en/slides/10.adjectivesfirsec/concl.html"
					}
				]
			}	
		]
	},
	{	
		"title": "Imperfect Indicative Active",
		"modules": [
			{
				"title": "Imperfect Indicative Active",
				"vocab": [""],
				"slides": [
					{
						"type": "slide_info",
						"includeHTML": "/static/content/en/slides/11.imperfectindicativeactive/intro.html"
					},
					{
						"type": "slide_info",
						"includeHTML": "/static/content/en/slides/11.imperfectindicativeactive/history.html"
					},
					{
						"type": "slide_info",
						"includeHTML": "/static/content/en/slides/11.imperfectindicativeactive/imperfindact.html"
					},
					{
						"type": "slide_info",
						"includeHTML": "/static/content/en/slides/11.imperfectindicativeactive/imperfindact1.html",
						"smyth": "s1889",
						"tasks": ["identify_morph_person", "identify_morph_number"]
					},
					{
						"type": "slide_info",
						"includeHTML": "/static/content/en/slides/11.imperfectindicativeactive/imperfindact2.html",
						"smyth": "s768#c",
						"tasks": ["identify_morph_person", "identify_morph_number"]
					},
					{
						"type": "slide_info",
						"includeHTML": "/static/content/en/slides/11.imperfectindicativeactive/concl.html"
					}
				]
			}	
		]
	},
	{	
		"title": "Third Declension: Consonant Stem",
		"modules": [
			{
				"title": "Third Declension: Consonant Stem",
				"slides": [
					{
						"type": "slide_info",
						"includeHTML": "/static/content/en/slides/12.thirddecconson/intro.html"
					},
					{
						"type": "slide_info",
						"includeHTML": "/static/content/en/slides/12.thirddecconson/history.html"
					},
					{
						"type": "slide_info",
						"includeHTML": "/static/content/en/slides/12.thirddecconson/thirddeccon.html"
					},
					{
						"type": "slide_info",
						"includeHTML": "/static/content/en/slides/12.thirddecconson/thirddeccon1.html"
					},
					{
						"type": "slide_info",
						"includeHTML": "/static/content/en/slides/12.thirddecconson/excep.html"
					},
					{
						"type": "slide_info",
						"includeHTML": "/static/content/en/slides/12.thirddecconson/thirddeccon_pent.html"
					}
				]
			}	
		]
	}
]
